<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    
    
    
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
           About # I&amp;rsquo;m Walter (the fifth). I like music and programming. What more can I say?
I work toward the best product possible by effectively planning, progressing in thoughtful increments, and choosing the right tools from the beginning.
Every project is a learning opportunity.
I value efficiency, functionality, and honesty over modern and flashy.
Education # Miami University, Oxford OH &amp;ndash; Computer Science B.S. (Honors) 2021, Magna Cum Laude UCHS, Liberty, IN &amp;ndash; Core 40 Honors 2017, Class Valedictorian Full Resume # LinkedIn Github Gitlab Instagram 
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/code-projects/dorkbash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code-projects/dorkbash/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
           dorkbash # A (very irresponsible) zork-like game written only in Bash
Dumb practice with shell language. Turns out you can do some bizarre things with a shell language, and it definitely teaches you to vet &amp;ldquo;bugs&amp;rdquo; because you&amp;rsquo;re leveraging features no should probably use.
GitHub See the code on GitHub 
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/code-projects/focustube/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code-projects/focustube/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
           focustube # A streamlined YouTube experience in React
In order to brush up on my React skills, I decided to make essentially a YouTube clone, but that intends to let the user search only for needed videos, queue them, and watch them without the added distraction of external ads and the recommendation algorithm.
Written in React Bootstrap, gh-pages, some npm utilities in the background Mobile first responsive YouTube Data API v3 and IFrame embedded API Live on GitHub pages GitHub See the code on GitHub 
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/code-projects/gravitygame/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code-projects/gravitygame/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Gravity Game # A work in progress physics-aware, space-themed FPS in Godot
This has been a good opportunity to work with someone else remotely, think about pipeline optimizations/version control, learn new tools, and play more with multiplayer programming. I have implemented simple multiplayer in the Unity engine, but at this point in Godot the only way is to start with RPC calls, which are lower level than built-in replication systems of Unity or Unreal.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/code-projects/harmonyv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code-projects/harmonyv/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
           Harmony V # A work in progress monophonic harmonizer plugin
There are many methods of pitch detection and shifting one could use, and the plugins I mean to emulate likely employ trade secrets that had an R&amp;amp;D team to produce, so this one is a slow challenge.
C++ Juce audio framework GitHub See the code on GitHub 
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/code-projects/infilerefactor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code-projects/infilerefactor/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
           Infile Refactor # Python CLI/GUI tool to find/replace but in multiple files within a file system (resursively)
Really nice for when file paths or variable names have changed and you want to fix it in one sweep without relying on an IDE or some other system.
Python 3 PySide 6 (for QT gui) GitHub See the code on GitHub 
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
           Code Projects # Projects which may or may not display my skills and interests
focustube # Gravity Game # dorkbash # Harmony V # Infile Refactor # Tooling I have used # Web General Purpose APIs and Libraries Game Engines 
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Music Examples # Hello there
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>